<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BA TECHNOLOGY</string>
    <string name="app_version">Version 1.0</string>

    <!-- developer details -->

    <string name="developer_email">gauravbordoloi@gmonetix.com</string>
    <string name="copyright">Copyright © 2017 BA TECHNOLOGY. \nAll Right Reserved.</string>

    <!-- Website Details -->
    <string name="terms_conditions">Welcome to BA TECHNOLOGY!\r\n\r\nThese terms and conditions outline the rules and regulations for the use of BA TECHNOLOGY\'s Website. \r\nBA TECHNOLOGY is located at:\r\n367,Thiruvalluvar st , \r\nChennai, Tamil Nadu 600017\r\nIndia\r\nBy accessing this website we assume you accept these terms and conditions in full. Do not continue to use BA TECHNOLOGY\'s website if you do not accept all of the terms and conditions stated on this page.\r\nThe following terminology applies to these Terms and Conditions, Privacy Statement and Disclaimer Notice and any or all Agreements: \"Client\", \u201CYou\u201D and \u201CYour\u201D refers to you, the person accessing this website and accepting the Company\u2019s terms and conditions. \"The Company\", \u201COurselves\u201D, \u201CWe\u201D, \u201COur\u201D and \"Us\", refers to our Company. \u201CParty\u201D, \u201CParties\u201D, or \u201CUs\u201D, refers to both the Client and ourselves, or either the Client or ourselves. All terms refer to the offer, acceptance and consideration of payment necessary to undertake the process of our assistance to the Client in the most appropriate manner, whether by formal meetings of a fixed duration, or any other means, for the express purpose of meeting the Client\u2019s needs in respect of provision of the Company\u2019s stated services\/products, in accordance with and subject to, prevailing law of India. Any use of the above terminology or other words in the singular, plural, capitalisation and\/or he\/she or they, are taken as interchangeable and therefore as referring to same.\r\n\r\nCookies\r\n\r\nWe employ the use of cookies. By using BA TECHNOLOGY\'s website you consent to the use of cookies in accordance with BA TECHNOLOGY\u2019s privacy policy.\r\n\r\nMost of the modern day interactive web sites use cookies to enable us to retrieve user details for each visit. Cookies are used in some areas of our site to enable the functionality of this area and ease of use for those people visiting. Some of our affiliate \/ advertising partners may also use cookies.\r\n\r\nLicense\r\n\r\nUnless otherwise stated, BA TECHNOLOGY and\/or it\u2019s licensors own the intellectual property rights for all material on BA TECHNOLOGY. All intellectual property rights are reserved. You may view and\/or print pages from http:\/\/batechnology.org for your own personal use subject to restrictions set in these terms and conditions.\r\n\r\nYou must not:\r\n\r\nRepublish material from http:\/\/batechnology.org\r\nSell, rent or sub-license material from http:\/\/batechnology.org\r\nReproduce, duplicate or copy material from http:\/\/batechnology.org\r\nRedistribute content from BA TECHNOLOGY (unless content is specifically made for redistribution).\r\n\r\nUser Comments\r\n\r\nThis Agreement shall begin on the date hereof.\r\nCertain parts of this website offer the opportunity for users to post and exchange opinions, information, material and data (\'Comments\') in areas of the website. BA TECHNOLOGY does not screen, edit, publish or review Comments prior to their appearance on the website and Comments do not reflect the views or opinions of BA TECHNOLOGY, its agents or affiliates. Comments reflect the view and opinion of the person who posts such view or opinion. To the extent permitted by applicable laws BA TECHNOLOGY shall not be responsible or liable for the Comments or for any loss cost, liability, damages or expenses caused and or suffered as a result of any use of and\/or posting of and\/or appearance of the Comments on this website.\r\nBA TECHNOLOGY reserves the right to monitor all Comments and to remove any Comments which it considers in its absolute discretion to be inappropriate, offensive or otherwise in breach of these Terms and Conditions.\r\nYou warrant and represent that:\r\nYou are entitled to post the Comments on our website and have all necessary licenses and consents to do so;\r\nThe Comments do not infringe any intellectual property right, including without limitation copyright, patent or trademark, or other proprietary right of any third party;\r\nThe Comments do not contain any defamatory, libelous, offensive, indecent or otherwise unlawful material or material which is an invasion of privacy\r\nThe Comments will not be used to solicit or promote business or custom or present commercial activities or unlawful activity.\r\nYou hereby grant to BA TECHNOLOGY a non-exclusive royalty-free license to use, reproduce, edit and authorize others to use, reproduce and edit any of your Comments in any and all forms, formats or media.\r\nHyperlinking to our Content\r\n\r\nThe following organizations may link to our Web site without prior written approval:\r\nGovernment agencies;\r\nSearch engines;\r\nNews organizations;\r\nOnline directory distributors when they list us in the directory may link to our Web site in the same manner as they hyperlink to the Web sites of other listed businesses; and\r\nSystemwide Accredited Businesses except soliciting non-profit organizations, charity shopping malls, and charity fundraising groups which may not hyperlink to our Web site.\r\nThese organizations may link to our home page, to publications or to other Web site information so long as the link: (a) is not in any way misleading; (b) does not falsely imply sponsorship, endorsement or approval of the linking party and its products or services; and (c) fits within the context of the linking party\'s site.\r\nWe may consider and approve in our sole discretion other link requests from the following types of organizations:\r\ncommonly-known consumer and\/or business information sources such as Chambers of Commerce, American Automobile Association, AARP and Consumers Union;\r\ndot.com community sites;\r\nassociations or other groups representing charities, including charity giving sites,\r\nonline directory distributors;\r\ninternet portals;\r\naccounting, law and consulting firms whose primary clients are businesses; and\r\neducational institutions and trade associations.\r\nWe will approve link requests from these organizations if we determine that: (a) the link would not reflect unfavorably on us or our accredited businesses (for example, trade associations or other organizations representing inherently suspect types of business, such as work-at-home opportunities, shall not be allowed to link); (b)the organization does not have an unsatisfactory record with us; (c) the benefit to us from the visibility associated with the hyperlink outweighs the absence of BA TECHNOLOGY; and (d) where the link is in the context of general resource information or is otherwise consistent with editorial content in a newsletter or similar product furthering the mission of the organization.\r\n\r\nThese organizations may link to our home page, to publications or to other Web site information so long as the link: (a) is not in any way misleading; (b) does not falsely imply sponsorship, endorsement or approval of the linking party and it products or services; and (c) fits within the context of the linking party\'s site.\r\n\r\nIf you are among the organizations listed in paragraph 2 above and are interested in linking to our website, you must notify us by sending an e-mail to info@batechnology.org. Please include your name, your organization name, contact information (such as a phone number and\/or e-mail address) as well as the URL of your site, a list of any URLs from which you intend to link to our Web site, and a list of the URL(s) on our site to which you would like to link. Allow 2-3 weeks for a response.\r\n\r\nApproved organizations may hyperlink to our Web site as follows:\r\n\r\nBy use of our corporate name; or\r\nBy use of the uniform resource locator (Web address) being linked to; or\r\nBy use of any other description of our Web site or material being linked to that makes sense within the context and format of content on the linking party\'s site.\r\nNo use of BA TECHNOLOGY\u2019s logo or other artwork will be allowed for linking absent a trademark license agreement.\r\n\r\nIframes\r\n\r\nWithout prior approval and express written permission, you may not create frames around our Web pages or use other techniques that alter in any way the visual presentation or appearance of our Web site.\r\n\r\nContent Liability\r\n\r\nWe shall have no responsibility or liability for any content appearing on your Web site. You agree to indemnify and defend us against all claims arising out of or based upon your Website. No link(s) may appear on any page on your Web site or within any context containing content or materials that may be interpreted as libelous, obscene or criminal, or which infringes, otherwise violates, or advocates the infringement or other violation of, any third party rights.\r\n\r\nReservation of Rights\r\n\r\nWe reserve the right at any time and in its sole discretion to request that you remove all links or any particular link to our Web site. You agree to immediately remove all links to our Web site upon such request. We also reserve the right to amend these terms and conditions and its linking policy at any time. By continuing to link to our Web site, you agree to be bound to and abide by these linking terms and conditions.\r\n\r\nRemoval of links from our website\r\n\r\nIf you find any link on our Web site or any linked web site objectionable for any reason, you may contact us about this. We will consider requests to remove links but will have no obligation to do so or to respond directly to you.\r\n\r\nWhilst we endeavour to ensure that the information on this website is correct, we do not warrant its completeness or accuracy; nor do we commit to ensuring that the website remains available or that the material on the website is kept up to date.\r\n\r\nDisclaimer\r\n\r\nTo the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, we exclude all representations, warranties and conditions relating to our website and the use of this website (including, without limitation, any warranties implied by law in respect of satisfactory quality, fitness for purpose and\/or the use of reasonable care and skill). Nothing in this disclaimer will:\r\n\r\nlimit or exclude our or your liability for death or personal injury resulting from negligence;\r\nlimit or exclude our or your liability for fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation;\r\nlimit any of our or your liabilities in any way that is not permitted under applicable law; or\r\nexclude any of our or your liabilities that may not be excluded under applicable law.\r\nThe limitations and exclusions of liability set out in this Section and elsewhere in this disclaimer: (a) are subject to the preceding paragraph; and (b) govern all liabilities arising under the disclaimer or in relation to the subject matter of this disclaimer, including liabilities arising in contract, in tort (including negligence) and for breach of statutory duty.\r\n\r\nTo the extent that the website and the information and services on the website are provided free of charge, we will not be liable for any loss or damage of any nature.</string>

    <!-- navigation menu -->

    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_services">Services</string>
    <string name="title_contact_us">Contact Us</string>

    <!-- main toolbar menu -->

    <string name="title_about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="title_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- settings -->

    <string name="pref_group_profile">PROFILE</string>
    <string name="pref_title_name">Your Name</string>
    <string name="default_your_name"> </string>
    <string name="pref_title_email">Your Email</string>
    <string name="default_your_email"> </string>
    <string name="pref_group_others">OTHERS</string>
    <string name="pref_title_copyright">Copyright</string>
    <string name="pref_title_dev_email">Developer Email</string>
    <string name="pref_title_build">Build Version</string>
    <string name="pref_title_term">Term &amp; Policies</string>
    <string name="default_your_number"> </string>
    <string name="pref_title_number">Your Phone Number</string>

    <!-- services -->

    <string name="web_development">WEB DEVELOPMENT</string>
    <string name="e_commerce_solution">E-COMMERCE SOLUTION</string>
    <string name="mobile_app_dev">MOBILE APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT</string>
    <string name="seo">SEARCH ENGINE OPTIMIZATION</string>
    <string name="logo_branding">LOGO &amp; BRANDING</string>

    <string name="web_development_summary">Batechnology offers wide-ranging web development services. We integrate advanced web technologies for interactive website development.</string>
    <string name="e_commerce_solution_summary">Batechnology designs and develop world class ecommerce Web sites, marketplace, B2B and B2C portals auction Web sites and much more.</string>
    <string name="mobile_app_dev_summary">Batechnology  recognizes the growing importance and relevance of mobile applications will account for 50% of the ecommerce sales by 2015.</string>
    <string name="seo_summary">Search engine optimization is a very important component of wholesome Internet marketing efforts.</string>
    <string name="logo_branding_summary">Brand Stories are not told bluntly, they require a certain sense of expertise to get them right.</string>

    <string name="web_development_content_url">file:///android_asset/services_web_dev.html</string>
    <string name="e_commerce_solution_content_url">file:///android_asset/services_ecommerce.html</string>
    <string name="mobile_app_dev_content_url">file:///android_asset/services_mobile_dev.html</string>
    <string name="seo_content_url">file:///android_asset/services_seo.html</string>
    <string name="logo_branding_content_url">file:///android_asset/services_logo_branding.html</string>

    <string name="web_development_content_browser_url">http://batechnology.org/web-development/</string>
    <string name="e_commerce_solution_content_browser_url">http://batechnology.org/services/e-commerce-solution/</string>
    <string name="mobile_app_dev_content_browser_url">http://batechnology.org/mobile-application-development/</string>
    <string name="seo_content_browser_url">http://batechnology.org/search-engine-optimization/</string>
    <string name="logo_branding_content_browser_url">http://batechnology.org/logo-and-branding/</string>

    <string name="about_us">file:///android_asset/about_us.html</string>

    <string name="fab_menu_close">Close</string>

    <string name="service_type_spinner">Please specify the service you want</string>

    <string name="permission">Please grant the permission to allow the app to run smoothly</string>
</resources>
